Guide to the Jack Censer collection, 1953-2011
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 6: Audiovisual materials, 2001-circa 2010s (Box 45)
  - WP, Word, Eudora, CD, November 2004 (Box 45)
  - Eudora, CD, December 27, 2004 (Box 45)
  - Jack's Eudora Out, CD, 2002 (Box 45)
  - Eudora mail, CD, July 4, 2004 (Box 45)
  - Eudora Outbox, CD, 2005 (Box 45)
  - Jack's Out, CD, 2003 (Box 45)
  - Word, CD, May 2004 (Box 45)
  - The Sniper' graphics, CD, April 2, 2009 (Box 45)
  - Index of WP (Washington Post) sniper stories, a list with annotation, CD, circa mid-2000s (Box 45)
  - DSS Data files folders A, B, C, D, E, CD, circa 2000s-2010s (Box 45)
  - Dan Domenech/ Ackland B, audiocassette, October 9, 2003 (Box 45)
  - Dan Domenech, audiocassette, October 9, 2003 (Box 45)